Michael L. Johnson

213-926-0655 MikeyLashaun@icloud.com 315 W. Queen St., Unit B Inglewood, CA 90301

Linkedin GitHub Portfolio

Profile

Very strong organizational skills, ability to pick up new processes and procedures quickly, extremely social, highly motivated, team worker, and dedicated to completing the task at hand. I have worked a multitude of jobs, all in which requires me to have excellent customer service personality.

Skills

- Resourceful problem solver
- Adaptable
- Organizational Skills:
 - Time Management
 - Assertive
 - Hands On worker

Experience

STUDENT, UCLA EXTENSION WESTWOOD, CA MAY 2021

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- GitHub
- jQuery
- API
- Handlebars
- Express
- Node
- MySQL
- Bootstrap
- REACT
- Mongoose

213-926-0655 MikeyLashaun@icloud.com 315 W. Queen St., Unit B Inglewood, CA 90301 Linkedin GitHub Portfolio

RECEPTION, (FELKER, TOCKZEK, SUDDLESON, ABRAMSON, LLP) LOS ANGELES, CA JUNE 2018-2021

- Received all incoming calls and directed to needed personal.
- Extensive work in Outlook, iManagement, and iEntertainment.
- Worked on Excel to log incoming checks and W2 statements.
- Assistant to Office Manager, Accountant, and Administrator.
- Created Invoices for clients.
- Data Management for new and existing clients in iEntertainment.
- Manage postal service for income and outgoing mail.
- Troubleshooting technical problems in office.
 - Computer problems
 - Printer problems
 - Phone issues
 - Server Mangement

BARTENDER, BENIHANA'S, SANTA MONICA, CA JUNE 2016-2019

- Able to craft a variety of cocktails, shooters, and mixed drinks.
- Do to the nature of the position I am excellent at serving lunch and dinner courses. Also, bussing my bar and tables surrounding it.
- Restocking and prepping for future incoming customers.
- Taking and recording inventory.
- Able to pour and serve draft beers correctly.

DISK JOCKEY (DJ) LIVE ENGINEER, YNOT ENERTAINMENT, LOS ANGELES, CA – MAY 2008-2020

- Lapprenticed with two DJ's.
- Calculating the demographics of a facility to set up DJ equipment, i.e., speakers, bass cabinets, lights, mixer, turntables, to achieve the best auditory harmonics.
- Master of Ceremonies; catering ceremonies to fit the demographic of the crowd.

Michael L. Johnson

213-926-0655 MikeyLashaun@icloud.com 315 W. Queen St., Unit B Inglewood, CA 90301

<u>Linkedin GitHub Portfolio</u>

- Playing music to fit the setting in mood of the occasion.
- Inventory control of equipment.
- Purchasing goods and equipment.

FOOD CARRIER, GRUBHUB, SANTA MONICA, CA – FEBRUARY 2015- APRIL 2016

DECISION MAKING IN ORDER TO ASSURE PROPER TIME MANAGEMENT FOR THE TIMELY PICKING UP AND DELIVERY OF FOOD.

- Regular and ongoing communication between employer and customers.
- Solving delivery problems due to restaurant delays, traffic, etc.
- Building professional and collaborative relationships with the restaurants and customers as representing the face of GrubHub and myself.

DRIVER, LYFT, SANTA MONICA, CA- MAY 2014- FEBRUARY 2015

- Built versatile customer interactions to establish inviting atmospheres.
- Set my own schedule/timetable.
- Chose work locations based on demand.
- Helped customers with packages/luggage.

ASSISTANT A&R, SONY RECORDS, BURBANK, CA - JUNE 2013- MAY 2014

- Internship which involved:.
 - Screened issues before they met the manager. Planned and reviewed the schedule for each day.
 - Constant note taking and reminder settings in a very interactive environment.
 - Personal driver to all events of the day.
 - Created charts and background information regarding our artist in scope.
 - Drafted and responded to artist, producers, and other crucial cliental.
 - Filtered instrumentals and lyrics before reaching further in the process.

CREW MEMBER, MCDONALDS, LOS ANGELES, CA - JUNE 2011-DECEMBER 2012

- Frequently rotated in the following work stations/job duties:
 - Front counter,
 - Drive through window,

Michael L. Johnson

213-926-0655 MikeyLashaun@icloud.com 315 W. Queen St., Unit B Inglewood, CA 90301

Linkedin GitHub Portfolio

- Kitchen worker/cook.
- Helped drive sales goals and achieve monthly standard for the mystery shopper.
- Resolved customer complaints and conflicts.
- Restocking and documenting all product.
- I worked on a very flexible schedule and was able to take all shifts from opening, closing, weekend, and holidays.

Education

UCLA Extension, Westwood, California - Full Stack bootcamp May, 2021

Santa Monica College, Santa Monica, California – Associates in Computer Science May, 2018 to Present

Santa Monica College, Santa Monica, California – Music Major, Business Minor May, 2013 to 2016

Santa Monica College, Santa Monica, California – Art Major, Music Minor May, 2010 to 2013